um
speaking a lot about Yoni Salman Sakara
through the
the like concurrent attention
um
to me it seems like there are a few ways
that you can talk about it to kind of
bridge into the subject
um peripheral awareness and being one
and um
um
I know they pointed the same thing but
they seem fairly different
um
when I hear peripheral it it turns into
trying to include it yeah
um
if you could speak more about the
definition yeah well concurrent the
um
it's like it's it's the
the most important factor that in a
sense that a beautician can develop that
so it's not something like
is only the right of you in order to
understand it it's a prerequisite
product View
so
um
so how can teach you to do that what
does he need to do that he's not doing
which would make him gain that vector
are two factors for the rising of the
Right View
Young Summer and right instruction
outlands of another so correct correct
information now you could argue that you know there
now you could argue that you know there
is the correct information you know you
could find it but it's still not
it's still not result in the Right View
but as long as that I would call it
concurrent attention or
Municipal is not developed so
what is that thing that the protagoner
could start doing that he's not doing
that can Aid and eventually
result in Arizona
who's transactions sorry mystery in his
actions yes that would be the starting
point then obviously look further
his intentions Beyond his actions and so
on but all of that supports
um supports your instrument it was
supposed to development but in and of
itself will not necessarily result in
development it's it's really like concurrent
it's it's really like concurrent
attention it's really more like a pagan
attitude with a certain attitude
with a certain attitude
certain attitude towards what
your experience as a whole yeah anything
that surprised exactly anything anything
called mental
emotionalism so your attitude
towards any manifested phenomenon
what how would you describe that that's
true or what idea would you have
in terms of what do you think it is
so attitude towards any other reason
Dharma what kind of attitude they went to is
what kind of attitude they went to is
there any reason down as necessary
is one of the factors for the right
review
terrorism by itself
yeah so
so
seeing it in during their present
manifested to its own extent so to speak
to its own extent so to speak
that's like what in philosophy
was kind of referred to as phenomena and
feminology recognizing things as
phenomena because it seemed like when an untrained
because it seemed like when an untrained
mind would have thoughts say about
Pleasant or unpleasant things
experiences memories future trends
they are not seen as phenomena
they might not necessarily deny the
existence of the results but they don't
see them in the right place so usually
he will be seen against like a backdrop
of a view that other thoughts are in my
head take this secondary to to this
material world that's the real measure
of existence
saying we want feelings for example
intentions are generally like oh this is
some movement of some energies and
what's not but the real reality is you
know the measurable World of Science and
so on the palpable stuff that we can
access to our census that's what's real
all of this is sort of secondary to it
yet here you are
having sleepless nights on account of
yours not real thoughts that are they
don't have the material aspects to them
yet they're equally real
so it's the the realization that
whatever it's manifested to whatever
extent on any to whatever level so to
speak is real as such to that level
it exists on its own regardless of you
and your perception of the world and
that I mean I don't mean like it exists
after me or before me because that will
be again that external perception of the
world independent on you know a present
president during feelings for example
president enduring thoughts or a mood
it's real as such in its own domain
because if it's not real as such
if it's not perceived
how do you know about modular how do you
know what thoughts you to have you are
perceiving it
he says that obviously through
non-restraint pursuit of sensuality
development of all the wrong views
towards on the on the base on the basis
of perverted order of sense organs and
sense bases sorry sense objects and
sense bases
you sort of uh you dismiss this do you
just see positive you see past is
these phenomena they are very real and
actually the kind of even more real than
than the world you assume it's real
they're the closest to you and uh
and uh
so so that's that's really the attitude
and you realize yeah a person can
develop it so you need some instruction
for it obviously
uh you need to understand and then you
need to start just practicing seeing
things on their own level to the extent
that they are
um and that's that's a good amount in
the suit that's when it says whatever
form there is past future present big small
there is past future present big small
far near subtle course whatever feeling
saying past future present not down left
in any form any shape any extent he
knows but it stands as it is
and that that means it means like his
view of recognizing things for the way
they risen is unshakable it's
established so he cannot not see things
as phenomenal
but saying oh
um
somebody who is familiar with parology
can know what that means but most people
are not familiar with it so then they
will just study phenomenology without
the Unison without authenticity get a
degree in phenomenology an indistential
philosophy and so on and think they
understood it but it's not about like
yes as I said there is a degree of
information you need but then you need
to start doing it like phenomenology
it's not a philosophy it's an attitude
it's an attitude of kind of initially
how how the the
person who founded it well that he's
considered as a Founder Edmund huser he
said he described it as stacked him back
that's it putting putting the world in
the back it's putting your experience in
the brackets in other words you step
from whatever it's Heavenly absorbing
you you unabsorb yourself from it to
gain perspective and that he didn't I
mean he took it in his own way like he
he drew he drawn some accurate
conclusions but then kind of fell into
views and started interpreting it again
with each kind of external secondary
principles Notions but certain people
recognize the value of no no
whatever views you might have actually
put it aside and just constantly
unabsorb yourself from whatever whatever
your attention is becoming absorbed
and that's exactly what the honest kind
of means means attending to whatever
you're attending but with the
perspective of the source of the womb of
the origin you can't attend the origin
because that becomes the object of your
attention so that's why I was saying the
reason I know it's not scholastically
accurate when I say concurrent attention
but I'm not as Scholastic dhamma is not
a Scholastic thing if you're studying
down scholastically you are not studying
the Dharma
I call it concurrent attention because
it revealed that concurrent to what
exactly comparing to what what could
current to yourself being unabsorbed
from whatever is trying to absorb you
and your attention will always going to
be resting on something
but it does not mean that you always
need to be absorbed unaware of yourself
in regard to whatever your attention is
resting on
so the beginning of fionis kind of the
beginning of that phenology the
beginning of stepping back unabsorbing
yourself in order to simultaneously have
a perspective endure there with whatever
you're attending so it will prevent you
from going too far down the rabbit hole
of absorbed tents that wants to pull it
and so on that's where the good exactly
said that there is no single thing that
brings desire to increase unriscent
desire to arise and a risen desire to
increase such as
without that Source not with the
concurrent intention and then there is
not a single thing that brings the
reason desire to decrease and none
reason to not arise such as yonis
romance that's now why is that so when lawn is
that's now why is that so when lawn is
happening from the ocean or when one is
attending concurrently yeah
let's go like this yeah with the
knowledge of the origin the knowledge of
the womb in other words with the
knowledge of the situation
simultaneously present with whatever
you're attending as an object of that
within that situation then why does
universe and sensual desire not revise
and a vision desire Sees God what no I'm
going to the question
somebody else can answer it yes exactly
so why is this so going on this
overlooking or not attending from the
origin there is a basically one
direction leave that way basically lost
on this recollect in the origin which
doesn't mean that the other direction
disappears you sound concrete attention
why is that sensual desire that is in
there not going to lies that way and if
it was there it's going to diminish why
thought is a few kind of put yourself
out in there with the things you can
almost just snowball with it and
um
with the involvement there's
you get caught up in something that that
you don't necessarily have to be caught
up in
um
response
it's not because it is like in Broad
Strokes yeah it does it does
he does pull you in so to speak um go
go
which I was gonna say with like with
perspective of a of something pressure
in you you realize it's pressuring you
so that whole pressure in aspect of it
won't be seen if you tend to it I only
saw it yeah
when you're establishing so the pressure
will be felt as pressure versus
you're by being a step established in
the only so you are already
um you already stepped you're already
you you break it the pressure as well
it's another thing that's risen which
you see is so you might not know that
you might not know you might not see the
implications of it by by practicing
correctly you are also stepping back as
as I described from the pressure which
which is basically why you are otherwise
uh pulled by the pressure so when you
don't have perspective with regard to
the pressure one thing will pressure you
to the next thing to the next because
you're trying to outrun the pressure
you're always hurt almost otherwise
because that first step like let you
step into it so to speak so you one
stepped into you one step into it with
the ones even with the original pressure
will become depressurized because you
cease to provide food for it the fuel
for it
um and and that's exactly why and so as
I said you might not necessarily
understand the applications of it
immediately but if you stick to it and
that's why I put together an outsider
can free himself from centrality yeah if
he's authentic enough
he would eventually then see through and
see the nature of sincerity as
pressuring and unpleasant and a doubt
and a boil and adapt and everything else
they would have described it and
recognize all I need to do is uh not
maintain this uh concurrent intention in
regard to this perspective that's it all
I need to do is not ignore not not
ignore the fact what has a reason right
in front of me to the extent that it has
arisen you
and then the sensuality would eventually
completely lose the appeal
but here's another question
and that's why uh sensuality is in here
in Islam also
it's not because of its sense objects
it's because it requires lack of
perspective it requires
it requires entering upon that course of
pressure willingly to ignore it
and see whatever time each time you
ignore means to that extent you don't
see that thing as a phenomenon whatever
you ignore it to that extent there is
ionizo to that extent you have not seen
the thing that isn't to the extent that
it has arisen and that's where ignorance
is the most blameworthy root of all
problems
yeah I was actually going to ask
something along those lines like
um so
the desire for a sensual pleasure or for
sensuality is concerned with particular
things so to speak and their signs and
features but is it possible that when
one is attending from the origin which
is to attend to the totality of the
division experience
that can can that can that mode of
attention and then at the same time
dwell on signs and features of
particular things
module by dwell in them well like you
can only like pick them up yeah so so if
you're concerned with beautiful or ugly
of particular phenomena like phenomenal
attention and because that's how you get
absorbed and how you lose that origin
yeah um so that is so to be drawn that way is
um so that is so to be drawn that way is
to already not attend from the origin
exactly but when honest attending from
the origin that whole domain is still
there but but can you then pick up those
signs of features and and get lost in
that direction while we're currently
attending no no
exclusive yeah I wanted to get that yeah
um so so that's why when attending from
the origin the whole thing begins to
cool down because you can develop on the
totality so to speak you cannot Lose
Yourself within it and losing yourself
within it is the fuel for it yeah but
then the key thing is to not own that
origin and say yeah eventually yeah yeah like
and say yeah eventually yeah yeah like
you can't
see if you try to sort of right away
start not owning it and so on you would
be attending to that without
perspective without the only self yes he
won't be concurrent attention but if you
studied in it
and obviously sense restraint and a
correct mode of behavior would be
supporting that practice of putting
things in Brackets or step back yeah and
allowing it to endure from what you step
back not to fix strange psychologize
modify cover up
um then yes you would be obviously
Discerning more and more so then you can
you can learn how to now put this more
refined aspects into brackets because
they are really such
that's why I keep saying whatever you
know like even if it's like some
ambiguous sense feeling or something oh
the degree of its ambiguity it's really
such it does not require clarification
in terms of making it into something
more palpable do you realize
clarification is on the level of not
ignoring even unclear things and this
phenomenon is unclear it is really such
yeah and that's quite clear and and by
regarding things this way
exactly that's why that the mundane
Right View developed like this it's like
pretty much paid with sense restraint
and everything else would have to result
into the right way of practice because
that's that's what's lacking
yeah there is there is instruction there
are suitors there are people that
practice restraint and keep the precepts
and so on but there are not many people
that know how to see things to the
extent that they have Arisen yeah
they're not many people they know that
they have to change their attitude and
recognize things existing as phenomena
phenomena independent of their sense of
their body and their mind both
just their given first beforehand
and then you realize oh this is first
whatever is manifested to the extent
it's manifested is the experience as a
whole is the totality of experience
any notion I have in regarded that
second I am identity everything else yeah
I am identity everything else yeah
but in all in order for that to be set
into that right order yeah that that
attitude needs to have been thoroughly developed
needs to have been thoroughly developed
there's a Mississippi government on the
basic mode of attending exactly exactly
outside of the uh the precepts the
restraint would you say also
I think you said it in one of the talks
just questioning questioning yourself
like who am I type of like questioning
what is this what's the
the meaning of this
automatically forces you to
head that direction so to speak like
a question
okay because
um it would force probably you because
all of the other things you know about
it and what you should need what you
need to be looking for so then it could
probably result in that way but if you
just say somebody just question yourself
it would sooner or later become
mechanical questions and or mystical like just put
questions and or mystical like just put
yourself in a question in whatever
experience comes out of it and then the
first thing that happens that's out of
the ordinary will be the answer yeah
whatever it might be
but yes in principle yes the attitude of
questioning is the attitude of
mindfulness that's how you develop
certain kindness that's how I developed
um
through questioning and recollection
what am I doing what I'm gonna do with
like why am I doing it what's my like
all of these questions just to again
shed light back
onto the wider situation so that you
unabsorb yourself from whatever you
ended up because nature the nature of
the sense organs animal is just to to
fall into that Focus that means going
with the crane
so focusing being absorbed that's just
following the grain
and uh and you want to basically go
against that
so you can't just willingly unfocus
because that will become the object of
your focus new Focus
uh but then you realize oh but why do we
focus you can learn to see that's the
peripheral and that whole thing in other
words unfocused to the extent of
whatever you've been focusing at without
denying it without trying to replace it
that's what's meant by like a reference
point inside of the town instead of
practice and the whole thing of concurrent is the
and the whole thing of concurrent is the
while exactly that's what I mean because
if if and that's why I'm stressing the
concurrency of it because if I'm just
unfocusing from this without
concurrently knowing that what I'm
focusing is still there I would just be
replacing one Focus one thing I'm
focused on with another thing I'm
focused on and I'm still fooling around
exactly the same direction you're
actually not changing you're not going
against the grain you're just changing
the object of your focus
but if you do it concurrently you
realize it's not about changing the
object it's about Discerning that
peripheral to the object it's about
learning how to put it in a bracket
while it is there
to see it to its own extent you see this
phenomena independent of as I said the
world the space the time in that sense
the the body the eye and any Notions any
concepts oh this is first you can use
that only Zone to to the way it is
that's it
and when you get used to that that's by
the way that's where the work starts
that's not what it ends okay now the way
it is I saw things the way they are okay
so what are you doing now are you
practicing or you think you're
enlightened a thousand times more
exactly now you do it so to discern the
properties of that phenomenon that's
what dhamma the dhamma is based on the
word dhamma which means things
like the the mental objects are Damas
thoughts that's it that's what Damas are and you
that's it that's what Damas are and you
realize yeah everything is a phenomenon
physical phenomena mental phenomenon
everything has that aspect of an image
often enduring image phenomenal image so
it's been analogical image
um so understanding the characteristics
of that the nature of manifestation the
nature of furniture
duka everything else in regard to its
properties oh that's the way out that's
they're done
I having them as available to be seen as
Thomas I think they send that and the
appearance of another right instruction
pointing certain things among those
damas that you see now oh yeah you'll
have to write you because you have a
basis for it and you have the
instruction as to what you see
I found the difficult to regard the like
negative um as a real thing so to speak just
um as a real thing so to speak just
that's it that's it see anything less
present or or anything that that's uh
um Less in the center
of your perception exactly the attitude
is the attitude towards that it's all
this is less real
that's exactly what I mean learning how
to see things to the extent they are
real as such
real than what
so you can actually question yourself in
that regard see you recognize oh
regardless is less real
so you can't just will yourself I'll
stop doing this
no it's it's a result of groundly
attending to things but now that you
spotted it yep reflect on it why is this
like why does this feel less real
less real to what but if it's less real
how can I talk about it in this real
sense what am I thinking about all these
thoughts are pretty real feelings are
pretty real so less real becomes real as
such that's the point the attitude of less
that's the point the attitude of less
real is not something you need to change
you need to see that as a real
phenomenon and then you stop regarding
things as less real
I think what I'm bumping into is
maybe more along the lines of you know
there's thought of the origin but is
that the origin that I need to be
um the original is there something I
need to search for well like you can see
now that question implies that the
origin is outside of you so you're
seeking this origin from where
everything comes from you want to see
the origin as an object and that's
impossible so it's not the origin even
if you go to the OMG because you're
attending to this wrong way so there's
no origin there
so it's not like I have to stop that
thought you need to see the real as such and
you need to see the real as such and
that's the origin so origin is when you
don't overshoot or undershoot
origin is when you attend to a rival in
the middle for whatever it is handsome
it away
that's where the origin is
you you overshoot it it's another object
of your of your focus of your attention
you understood it saying it's another
object
so you find the origin note by well you
attend with the origin you learn how to
attend concurrently
not before or after
so comparing attention
is what the Onision is for you at the
time even if you don't think that's
where the Amazon is that's why it needs
repetition and training not just an
intellectual answer
because I say crack we're speaking
you're probably gonna have to do the
where you get sucked in and then you
step back out okay
pushing back that's why the precepts and
routing of the sensors and everything
it's just it's there like as a container
a gate that keeps you from like when
you're sucking from like going too far
yeah but it's never optional the body isn't
but it's never optional the body isn't
there or exactly within a feeling those
understandings those clarities with just
oh whenever actually I tend to describe
they're not bodies there but this does
itself almost up yeah yeah and that's
where you with that kind of that's where
you can become less involved so to speak
with seeing things that's phenomenal and
learning how to think rightly in other
words knowledge is taking over
so mindfulness is resulting in certain
perceptions becoming set now so even if
that's a southerner can become careless
and can proliferate his sensuality and
so on
but he cannot not see things as
phenomenal fundamentally
that he cannot go beyond below anymore
that's what it's meant he can't take any
Sankara as permanent or as as
pleasurable if he sees when he descends things he
if he sees when he descends things he
doesn't ignore things on the level of an
enduring phenomenon
will not cannot be taken as well it's
just impossible
he cannot go past that below that
threshold Gap
and so to understand and practice Jones
is necessary if a noble disciple is
going to develop satipatana because
those forces are almost substitutes the
whole principle of the origin knowing in
the concurrent attention yeah now this
this is yeah so yeah exactly so
realizing that that origin is
already there always anyway you now
realize what is always they are killing
their mother to solve the origin as well
yeah but yeah yeah
so that's how it starts not having
understood that one can then turn to
this that's bound to be go wrong yeah
exactly there's nothing to apply yeah so
the entire partition for the entire
practice of Dharma is within the
principle of God that's the whole thing
yeah yet it's taught us carefully attending
yet it's taught us carefully attending
to something yeah yeah but appropriately
attended wisely I mean none of that is
necessarily wrong
etymologically but it's like well what
does that mean what does appropriately
mean what does wisely mean whatever it
feels right now means it's right I'm
making the effort
no it's it's a it's an absolute
fundamental Factor the only space of
another gives rise to the to the right
view thus if somebody who is president
does not have the right view well it's
only because these two factors are
lacking or one of them cannot be a third
option can it be I have both factors but
I'm still not sorry inconceivable
yeah exactly exactly but we're talking
about how to translate it and then you
realize what whichever will translate it
you will have to qualify it because it's
it's not and it's not it's not on the
level of an answer to what it is it's on
the level of something that needs to be
done and repeated and attitude needs to
be reshaped towards your own experience
so it's phenomenal so for that you're
gonna need a lot more description than
just finding a perfect etymological
match or something but if you say to a
sort of planner attend appropriately or
attend boys
yeah because the main problem when
people were referring to it with like as
wise attention and sound the main
problem I kind of detected was it was it
was coming it was becoming something
that's that anybody can do on the level
of psychologization yeah
so I just need to wisely go through the
motions of telling myself what they said
hey this is good and I do this and
remind myself and go through the
recitations and so on and that's my
original cicada practice it's like no no
it's sympathetic they were by right
attitude makes sense to disappear
wrongly attending to it makes it
increase whether you talk about it or
not whether you have secondary thoughts
and plans and scenarios to scare you or
whatever just to put you off but that's
all way too far down the line
proliferate that's why on the level of
sense objects so in other words you
don't want to manage it you want to
approach it
yeah attention is basically gives rise to all
attention is basically gives rise to all
things how did other City says the boom
of it there is no deeper than that
so just to connect this with
the side of the Mind
it seems like a very closely intertwined
yeah developing Jonas on the basis of sensor
developing Jonas on the basis of sensor
strength of the sensor seclusion
as I said seeing anything that manifests
doesn't matter
direct if it's right in front of you or
at the back of your mind it is subtle or
coarse big or small ambiguous or clear
personal or impersonal you see it a
reason as such
and that's exactly how you can get the
spot to the mind
because mine is a phenomenon it's a
background of your mind basically it's
what the mind is the background of you
currently whatever absorb experience you
are that ambiguous kind of white
non-specific sense where your IM lingers
so to speak that's the mind
but it's all about investigating it
defining it it's about seeing it as such
so the signs of the mind not the signs
that I put in the mind
and that's that's exactly going to be
the result of that which is why sign of
the Mind needs to be seen before the
Right View as I said United is
developing the right attitude the
correct attitude towards any phenomenon
so once if you don't see the phenomenon
of the mind or mind as phenomena as an
enduring thing there in the background
how can you develop your attitude
towards it how can you train impossible
so that's why it's necessary sound like
the mind is necessary what would it say
no
that somebody can become accomplishing
the Right View having not grasped the
signs of the Mind such thing is not
possible yeah yeah and then signing
their mind only heals itself in security
it's inclusion yeah exactly
and you could describe like the the sign
of the Mind as uh point of view like
practically on a day-to-day basis there
is a sense of the direction of your view
the point of however you're attending
you just never again it's less real it
feels like it's frustrated and
everything else that you are attending
that's what one is attending lustful
things yeah versus things and then if
even if one stops attending that sure
you step back to a degree but then if
you don't go into seclusion
that point of view will still feel like
live stream less palpable gas means less
real even if you don't say I don't think
it means less real for me you imply that
it's less Real by being unclear about
its extent of its terminology
so whenever people have a conversation
with the Buddhism and they attain stream
entry right there and then
um
does that sort of just imply that before
meeting him they were already exactly
Aesthetics at some degree yeah okay I
mean was when he said the two factors for the
was when he said the two factors for the
stream entry
if those were not the only factors he
would have said oh that is
another factor for for the right view is
just being lucky to talk to me yeah
no he didn't say that so why do you talk
to the Buddha whether he
is extraction sure he'll be the most
accurate he'll know exactly what you
need to hear but if you haven't met him
halfway in other words if you have if
you don't have your own sikara he can be
talking all he wants you want to
understand has it happened with people
like he was actually instructing them
for the review and they didn't get it
because they haven't they were not
authentic they were not authentic
because they were not restrained they
were not restrained because they were
behaving and wholesome and not keeping
increases then it's covering it up team
talking about the the like
existentialists and the phenomenologists
um
what is the
distinction between a protugina whose
authenticity drives him crazy like
Nietzsche for example and
the one who you know becomes
you know starts dwelling in pajamas you
know he's a the reactions
the reactions
no go on their actions actions yeah
that would make them great because it's
so contradictory yeah
yeah yeah so just so the mind is going
on by that authentic anxiety if the
actions are not purified he actually the
purified mind can think it so you can
sort of develop a degree of authenticity
without yeah some people obviously are
you know
their faculties are sharper mines okay
it's like a different types of persons
like when he's talking about
something just practice your very little
instruction um you need a bit more sound as a method
um you need a bit more sound as a method
we have everything right there's still
ongoing a direction it's just hopeless
for the fact that somebody already can
recognize the value of the dhama has
inspiration the practice means open
apart from hopeless
but then yeah how much of that
um suffering and anxiety and we don't
really have been doing well that depends
on
uh how much of your actions need to be
purified and what purification means
restraints and then allowing the
pressure endure without acting out of it
taking responsibility for it seeing it
doesn't mean thank you not traveling it
up in the duty of tradition and virtue
and seniority and authority and scripts
yeah
presets and so on will not automatically
result in your Instagram
things like that
so I think we talked about this too I'm
going to take positive um
there isn't anything that really happens
when you do attend from the origin
like there's no
change in front he said like there's there's
in front he said like there's there's
nothing
perceptible to change it's really not
any probable on the levels yeah
and that's why people want this really
recognize the value of it is that there
are no players
like oh no no there is no novelty to it
and I was saying that before I gave that
similar up
waiting for a bus for there's no no my
bus stop
and it's like unless you know where you
should just kind of keep yourself done
okay I'll stay within this range yeah
so you do need to learn and then keep
doing it
and that's why as I said many times
right you cannot be obtained by accident
or magically
because who will by accident stay
practice that which has no immediate
power volume
verification and confirmation
this is why also this one Sita says that
it's Independence upon Faith
oh sorry what it says So based on faith
yes oh wow well there you go
I don't need to talk about it
you need to have a degree of Faith you
stay in that level yeah because
everything else is going to make him
make it positive yes get the sensations
get the overwhelming experience of your
meditation get the inspirational get
something that you can squeeze so to
speak something that you can see perceive in
something that you can see perceive in
that direct sense
so unless you have faith to ignore that
whole to not give in to that everything
spongy but you know it just feels so
real and staying with this that doesn't
feel quite real
repeatedly endure the pain on account of
it most people would probably have to
today it's like yeah without faith you won't
it's like yeah without faith you won't
do it
which means without the faith you won't
get away with
so it's difficult to recognize because
in a sense there's not enough to do it
but even then when discussing with
somebody you might actually recognize it
but then they don't interface to stay
with it so it's still no way yeah and
that's what I said like it's like you
know you need to repeat it so many times
as well
and I need to cultivate their attitude
so it grows and spreads and becomes more
fun
so that's why it's like
not on the level of answers and and kind
of
satisfactory pleasing figuring out of
the ideas that's that can contribute if
you figure out the right ideas but you
must think on the fact okay but now I
actually like to stop doing this yeah
whatever whatever is presently have
taken to be Focus already and they're
not finding specific objects sorry to be
attended or focused on
yeah less real I think that that really
sums it up for most people I think
that's exactly the main the core of the
protogenous problem and lack be honest
they don't recognize the things that are
less real are real as such
so they keep maintaining the threshold
the measure of what feels real for them
but feels really real they measure
things against that you know they don't
understand it well something less real
is still real as such
given this I will put it because you
find it difficult
that kind of indicates that it's real
it's a yeah exactly how could you even
talk about it it would not be manifested
image this is not real
repeated recognition of that there's
less real things are real as such
not real as much but real as such as
style that you use
for determining what is real
yeah I guess that that is why such a
strength comes to make
that standard to develop that standard
yeah exactly yeah
like
okay if this is difficult so something
which is easy is real which means that
will be cool yeah
and that's exactly why
's view is developed
you would overcome doubt
because the core
the the the the the source of power
without hairs it's exactly that
seeking what's really like palpable as
the answer and refusing to accept the
lack of clarity ambiguity it pressures
you and you automatically have to get
rid of that pressure
equals c less real means well
let's mine Less in my control
less confirming me exactly
doubt go hand in hand in that level you
know that extent
and we drove out from the put in the
world and the sense of Duty to avoid the
pressure of real or less real and doubt
syllabus the first three pages you can
see why they would come come it would
make sense even now when I'm discovering
why exactly they would be the first
three purpose to come off with
development to be honest when starting
the right construction yeah